<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="pretty-atom-feed.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>Blog Title</title>
  <subtitle>This is a longer description about your blog.</subtitle>
  <link href="https://example.com/feed/feed.xml" rel="self" />
  <link href="https://example.com/" />
  <updated>2025-02-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
  <id>https://example.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name>Your Name</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Thoughts &amp; Ramblings No. 1</title>
    <link href="https://example.com/blog/thoughts-and-ramblings-1/" />
    <updated>2025-02-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://example.com/blog/thoughts-and-ramblings-1/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Again another series/topic I am ripping off from others. I love a behind the scenes look at what other writers are up too. Dave Rupert’s Vibe Check (&lt;a href=&quot;https://daverupert.com/tag/vibecheck&quot;&gt;https://daverupert.com/tag/vibecheck&lt;/a&gt;) series is one that I like a lot. When I ready these it reminds me to take a step back and work on myself as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and keep track of all the media I consume...or at least try to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;movies&quot;&gt;Movies&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt4513678/?ref_=nv_sr_srsg_6_tt_8_nm_0_in_0_q_Ghostbu&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ghostbusters: Afterlife&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; ★★★☆☆
A movie I wanted to watch when it came out but missed. Overall I enjoyed it but felt like a movie for kids in a weird way. I did like McKenna Grace. Might watch Frozen Empire next.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;books&quot;&gt;Books&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bookshop.org/p/books/foundation-and-empire-isaac-asimov/11418077?ean=9780553293371&amp;amp;next=t&amp;amp;next=t&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Foundation and Empire&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; ★★★★★
I have slowly been reading the original Asimov &lt;em&gt;Foundation&lt;/em&gt; series after watching the show on Apple TV. These are way better stories and setting than the show. Which I like for different reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;tv&quot;&gt;TV&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I probably watch too much TV if I am honest but this month I mostly watched murder mysteries like Dagliesh from AcornTV. I recently started rewatching Dragonball Z as well! A real mix of shows. More to come.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am working on creating and building out a regular schedule for posting and what to post about. I should have a regular series about this site and the work I want to do to improve my skills but also this site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;gym&quot;&gt;Gym&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I spend my evenings at the gym where I hangout with my friends but also working on my fitness. These days I am working on Olympic Weightlifting and Brazilian Jiu Jitsu. Both have a balance of what my body and mind needs. I need&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cheers!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>2024</title>
    <link href="https://example.com/blog/2024/" />
    <updated>2025-01-14T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://example.com/blog/2024/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh man, what a year! I always read these types of posts when I come across my RSS feeds. A great way to check in with yourself and see how far you have come or not!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But this writing unlocks a real opportunity to reflect on life and whether or not we’re living in alignment with our values and enthusiasms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bradfrost.com/blog/link/2025-another-year-of-blog-on-the-desktop-again-live-laugh-blog/&quot;&gt;Brad Frost&lt;/a&gt; covers why I think this is a great type of writing and why I am writing my own post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2024 was a transitional year, but one that, as I look back, I see how much I grew this year. Growing my hobbies away from the computer and trying to rebuild some old and good habits like reading, journaling, and, you know, eating well. I had ups and downs on all of these, but I really enjoyed that path of discovering what did and did not work with these. Well, the eating well, I know about that I just…like chips…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Journaling is something I will probably touch on more in the future. My system is pretty simple and not elaborate as others. I try to keep it easy since I don’t want to waste too much time on something I think shouldn’t…blah blah…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Back to 2024…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I set some lofty goals for myself in 2024, and I think I got some, but I also didn’t, and that’s okay! I reset some goals and ambitions, and I feel like I am on a more fulfilling path heading into 2025. Kind of wild that a little reset and realignment can put you on a better path. My goals seem much more in line with what I want in life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, 2024 was a year of realignment, and 2025 I seek out to build on that realignment. I am ready to put in the work.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Welcome to my Weblog</title>
    <link href="https://example.com/blog/welcome-to-my-weblog/" />
    <updated>2025-01-04T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://example.com/blog/welcome-to-my-weblog/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;After many years of rambling about the open web and how I want to start writing more, I am finally starting that. I have enough brain space now to actually sit down and start getting thoughts out in this form. Also, time, but...you know...that is also a premium.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This whole process of getting from nothing to being able to write and get thoughts out has been an uphill battle. I really don&#39;t mind if anyone reads this. If you are reading this, &amp;quot;Hi!&amp;quot; I was trying to think about the goals for this and my site, and I went back into my reading list and remembered a post by &lt;a href=&quot;https://ethanmarcotte.com/wrote/let-a-website-be-a-worry-stone/&quot;&gt;Ethan Marcotte&lt;/a&gt; about his website being a &amp;quot;worry stone,&amp;quot; and when I reread that, it clicked with me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What clicked is...this is mine. This is where I should tinker. I have been looking for something that I could use myself and learn new skills. It could be writing, a new CSS trick I want to try out, or some new JavaScript that I want to work on. I have a list of 100 things I want to do and learn but have never found the space to do it in my day job. But here...here I can do that. I had fought to give myself the permission.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The other thing that clicked with me recently was...I miss the old web. I miss the personal feel of sites and the ownership. Now everything is being siloed off or walls being put in place to make sharing harder, and it sucks. A lot of the modern web just sucks, and I want to feel like I own at least a little part of it where my voice is the only one. I want this space to reflect who I am and what I am. It is going to be dirty and messy, and that excites me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am going to work towards that excitement.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>